oneview.com 2001-04-21

# Oneview - About Oneview

### Privacy Statement

Oneview is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many offers. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. We will also inform all users via email about fundamental changes.

If you have questions concerning our privacy statement, please contact [support@oneview.com](mailto:support@oneview.com). 

**Collection of personally identifiable information**

Oneview collects information in several ways. 

Some personal information is gathered when you register. During registration, Oneview asks for your name, email address and other personal information. Once you register you are no longer anonymous to Oneview - you are given a Oneview Login and are able to take full advantage of Oneview's offers. 

In addition to registration we may ask you for personal information at other times, including (but not limited to) when you enter a contest, when you use special additional Oneview offers and when you report a problem regarding our service. If you contact Oneview we may keep a record of that correspondence. Oneview also occasionally asks users to complete surveys that we use for statistical purposes. Wherever Oneview collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this privacy statement on that page. 

When you are on an Oneview site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Oneview alone. 

Please note that Oneview advertisers or web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those web sites linked to Oneview are not covered by this privacy statement. 

**Cookies**

Offering a personalized service, Oneview uses [cookies](http://www.zdwebopedia.com/cookie.htm). A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored in the browser's memory on your computer's hard drive. Oneview also works without using cookies except of somecomputer systems or if a proxy server is used. 

Oneview uses cookies to identify a user during the whole accessing process. Thus the user doesn't need to login everytime he visits a new personalized page. 

Advertising networks that serve ads onto Oneview may also use their own cookies. 

Oneview also collects IP adresses for system administration and for reportingaggregate information to our advertisers. 

**Usage of information**

Oneview's goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our service. In order to provide services free of charge, we display advertisements. By knowing a little about you, Oneview is able to deliver more relevant advertisements and content, and hence better service, to you. 

In our role of delivering targeted advertisements, Oneview plays the middleman. Advertisers give us an advertisement and tell us the type of audience they want to reach (for example, males over 35 years old). Oneview takes the advertisement and displays it to users meeting that criteria. In this process, the advertiser never has access to individual account information. Only Oneview has access to individuals' accounts. This kind of advertisement targeting is done with banner ads. You will receive special offers via email from Oneview only if you have indicated in your account preferences that you would like to receive them. You can change your account preferences at any time. 

Oneview does research on our users' demographics, interests and behavior based on the information provided to us upon registration and from our server log files. We do this to better understand and serve our users. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. 

**Sharing of Informationen**

As a general rule, Oneview will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances. Please see our Terms of Service for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared. For instance, Oneview may disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Oneview's Terms of Service or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Oneview's rights or property, other Oneview users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Oneview may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services. 

**Choices of the user regarding collection, use and distribution of information**

If you indicated upon registration that you are interested in receiving offers or information from Oneview and our partners, we may occasionally send you direct mail about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. 

Only Oneview (or agents working on behalf of Oneview and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings and only if you indicated that you do not object to these offers. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal information. 

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. 

**Update, correction and deletion of information**

You may edit your Oneview account informationen at any time in the "options"-area by using your Oneview login and password. If you have forgotten your password, please click "Forgot password?" click on our homepage next to the login form. For all other problems signing in to Oneview or signing out please contact [support@oneview.com](mailto:support@oneview.com). 

**Security precautions of Oneview to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information**

Your Oneview account information is password-protected so that you and only you have access to this personal information. 

We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Oneview will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to log out of your Oneview account and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Oneview cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

**Further information regarding privacy**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on the Oneview blackboard or via email - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. 

If you have questions concerning our privacy statement, please contact [support@oneview.com](mailto:support@oneview.com).
